Okay, so in the last video when we
submitted this form, it took us to a new
page and the way it did that is it
changed the URL from just being
localhost 5500 to localhost 5500 and
then passing over information for the
username and the password. Now one thing
that's a problem with this is my
password is now visible on the URL bar
and that's kind of problematic. Um, and
for another maybe the resource I'm using
on the back end needs this to come
across as a post request. So what it's
come across right now is this is called
a get request. One of the key things
about a git request is that it encodes
all of the data and puts it into the
URL. So when it gets sent over all of
this data is sent over and it's visible
to anybody who can see the URL. Um and
again that could be problematic. So what
we could do is we could change the type
of form this is and you could say what
method do I want it to use to send the
data. Well there are three options here.
There's get, post and dialogue. dialogue
means show a pop-up box on the screen.
Um, and you may remember this from when
we talked about modals. Um, but here I
am going to put post.
And so if I save this now, uh, let's go
back to our normal website and I put in
my username and put in my last name as a
password and hit submit.
Um, it says it tried to make a post
request and it didn't get anything back.
And that's because um it tried to talk
to a server that doesn't really exist.
Um right now we're just running this on
live server. Um and live server isn't
listening for post requests. It's
listening for get requests so that we
can find
a website, but it is not listening for
post requests like our API